Guide to the Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service records ARC.129
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 4: Photographs, 1920s-1986; V1991.110; 4 Linear Feet in eight boxes and one binder
  The lantern slides document life in Brooklyn in the 1920s and 1930s. They include images of tenements (interiors and exteriors), but also the construction of new buildings and what appear to be more affluent sections of the borough. Many of the slides were produced by the Devereaux View Company and James Huntington.
  The 35 mm slides are also primarily promotional in nature, and date from the 1950s to the 1970s.
  Twp additional photographic albums and scrapbooks can be found in Sub-series 1.5: Committee on the Blind and related events and Series 2: Brooklyn Children's Aid Society records.
  - Prints (Box Prints by Accession 58, Item V1991.110.276-304, Box Prints by accession 59, Item V1991.110.305, Box Prints by Accession 76, Item V1991.110.1-275)
  - Oversize prints (Box Prints by Accession OS13)
  - Lantern slides (Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39)
  - Slides, V1991.110 (Box Slides by Accession 4, Box 1-4, Item V1991.110.290.1-183)